<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

   <statements version="1.0" htmlParse="false">
     <statement id="1">I have sufficient language knowledge to teach senior levels.</statement>
     <statement id="2">Being able to speak fluently with native speakers is important to me.</statement>
     <statement id="3">Students often think language classes are unimportant.</statement>
     <statement id="4">Classroom management is an important part of language teaching.</statement>
     <statement id="5">Students have lower expectations of teachers who are non-native speakers.</statement>
     <statement id="6">I have reflected on how to teach about culture in my language classes.</statement>
     <statement id="7">I am confident to teach my TL in a classroom.</statement>
     <statement id="8">I use my TL in a variety of social contexts.</statement>
     <statement id="9">External language assessments/exams should be used to check a teacher's TL proficiency.</statement>
     <statement id="10">My primary/high school language teachers seemed to be engaged in improving their language teaching.</statement>
     <statement id="11">Parents regard non-native speakers as inferior to native speakers.</statement>
     <statement id="12">Teaching about cultural aspects is very motivating for students.</statement>
     <statement id="13">My language teacher identity is strongly influenced by my language learning experiences.</statement>
     <statement id="14">I feel confident about using my TL in a variety of social contexts</statement>
     <statement id="15">I am highly motivated to continually develop my knowledge of my TL.</statement>
     <statement id="16">Schools are not the best place to learn languages.</statement>
     <statement id="17">It's difficult to understand the culture embedded in a language if it's not your L1.</statement>
     <statement id="18">Maintaining networks for me to use the language regularly is important.</statement>
     <statement id="19">Building good relationships with students is the most important thing for a language teacher to teach effectively.</statement>
     <statement id="20">I feel confident about using my TL in a variety of formal contexts</statement>
     <statement id="21">All students can become successful language users.</statement>
     <statement id="22">Classroom management is harder for teachers who are non-native English speakers.</statement>
     <statement id="23">I am confident about integrating language and culture in my teaching.</statement>
     <statement id="24">Being multilingual is a strong marker of my identity.</statement>
     <statement id="25">I would feel comfortable using the TL anywhere in a school (e.g. staffroom, staff dining area) with other native/non-native speakers.</statement>
     <statement id="26">Language teaching will be a rewarding career.</statement>
     <statement id="27">Reflecting on my actions as a language teacher is a high priority for me</statement>
     <statement id="28">Native-like pronunciation is the best model for students.</statement>
     <statement id="29">It's sufficient for students to just learn about the mainstream culture linked to my TL.</statement>
     <statement id="30">Using the TL in regular classroom interactions will feel natural to me.</statement>
     <statement id="31">Using English is the most effective way to manage the classroom.</statement>
     <statement id="32">Most of my primary/high school language teachers were good at teaching.</statement>
     <statement id="33">Learning about culture is optional in language learning.</statement>
     <statement id="34">Language teachers are respected in schools.</statement>
     <statement id="35">My identity changes when I am using an L2.</statement>
     <statement id="36">I need to spend more time developing my TL proficiency.</statement>
     <statement id="37">External language assessments/exams should be used to check a teacher's knowledge of the TL grammar.</statement>
     <statement id="38">I need to spend more time developing my knowledge of TL grammar.</statement>
   </statements>